ANDREW ANC

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-anc-0911721a/

Github: https://github.com/aancjr

Portfolio: https://aancjr.github.io/Master-Portfolio/ Email: andrewancjr@gmail.com

Merrimac MA, 01860

Phone: 978.457.5782

SUMMARY

Full-stack developer educated at the University of New Hampshire Coding Bootcamp program with experience in front-end and back-end software languages. Success built by working closely with management, team and peers to resolve issues, increase customer satisfaction and build product confidence. Executes and accomplishes all tasks in a professional and timely manner, while working within deadlines. Uses positivity, motivation and willingness to learn in day-to-day workflow to be a strong team player and increase growth. Natural aptitude for technology and problem solving, life-long learner and an excellent communicator.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Scss.

Front-End Technologies: Bootstrap, jQuery, React.js.

Back-End Technologies: Express, Node, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, NPM Packages.

Other: Chrome Developer Tools, AJAX, Git.

PROJECTS

Canna-Keeper

Github: https://github.com/kylewhittemore/project-three
App: https://rocky-meadow-38771.herokuapp.com/

- Demo Login: Username: demo123 | Password: demo123
- Hobby cannabis growers go-to app to log, track and view information about their personal gardens. Images, data and charts are displayed in an easy to digest user experience, allowing for the user to improve their overall results.
- Languages Used: React.js, Express, MongoDB, NPM Packages, JWT, AWS, s3bucket, Scss.

Portfolio

Github: https://github.com/aancjr/Master-Portfolio Website: https://github.com/aancjr/Master-Portfolio/

- My portfolio page, dedicated to showcasing my projects, contact information and where you can find out a bit more about myself.
- Languages Used: HTML, CSS, JavsScript.

Crystal Collector

Github: https://github.com/aancjr/Crystal-Collector
App: https://github.com/aancjr/Crystal-Collector

- Web-based game where the user must click the correct sequence of gems to total the computer's guess.
- Languages Used: jQuery, JavaScript, CSS, HTML.

EXPERIENCE

Medical Account Executive Jan 2019 - Current | EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.

- Creating and maintaining customer relationships.
- Working closely with assigned territory representatives to strategically increase revenue.
- Building brand awareness and recognition among current and future customers.

Dealer Relations ManagerJuly 2018 - December 2018 | CarGurus, Inc. - Cambridge, MA.

- Maintained customer relationships, while educating and increasing software knowledge with key account contacts.

SSD Account Executive Jan 2018 - July 2018 | EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.

- Brand new role: Assisted management with developing and creating role strategy for increasing revenue for assigned products from strategic industry partners.

Elsevier Account Manager May 2014 - Jan 2018 | EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.

- 300% Sales Club Award: Exceeded 100%, 200% and 300% of my annual sales quota.

K-8 Account Executive Nov 2013 - May 2014 | EBSCO Information Services - Ipswich, MA.

- Exceeded role expectations by maintaining and growing K through 8th grade territory (50% of the US).

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp Certificate Bachelor's of Science in Business 2019 | University of New Hampshire - Portsmouth, NH. 2011 | Full Sail University - Winter Park, FL.